catertrax.com 2019-03-28

# CaterTrax Privacy Policy

## CaterTrax Respects Your Right to Privacy

This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to the information practices related to our website, [catertrax.com](http://catertrax.com/). Further, if you use our website ([catertrax.com](http://catertrax.com/), which is the site you’re reading this on at this very moment), then this page is for you. Among other things, it talks about what constitutes a legitimate use of our website. Although this website contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other sites. If you follow a link to another website you should carefully read their privacy policy.

## Personally Identifiable Information

Any personally identifiable information that you submit to our website will only be used to service your account and/or to provide you with information on CaterTrax products and services. The types of personal information that may be collected at our website include: name, address, email address and telephone number.

CaterTrax is the sole owner of all information collected on this site. CaterTrax will not rent, sell or share any personally-identifiable information about you with third parties for any reason except when required to assist in resolving an issue you raise with us or as required by law.

Information collected on this website is imported into Mailchimp. You can review Mailchimp’s privacy policy here: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

## Aggregate Information

We generally record certain usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to our website. This information may include the websites that you access immediately before or after your visit to the CaterTrax website, the Internet browser you are using and your IP address. We use this information for internal use to help us provide a better user experience and to determine what kinds of information our users may find useful. We will not disclose any of this non-personally-identifiable information to a third party. Again, this information does not identify users personally, only their general behavior while using the CaterTrax website.

Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive. Each website that you visit can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser preferences allow it. These cookies do not personally identify the user but only act to help us better understand user needs. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits.

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

The GDPR is a regulation intended to strengthen and unify data protection for everyone within the European Union (EU). We believe that all customers can benefit from its mandates which is why we are implementing the requirements of the EU’s GDPR. The GDPR requires greater openness and transparency from companies on how they collect, store and use personal data. You can learn more [here](https://catertrax.com/eugdpr/).

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

CaterTrax reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason. Please review this policy periodically for changes. A link to the current version of this Privacy Policy can be accessed from the footer of every page on this website. You acknowledge that by accessing this website after we have posted changes to this Privacy Policy, you are agreeing to the terms of the Privacy Policy as modified.

## Fair Processing Notice

The Personal Data CaterTrax Inc. (“CaterTrax”) collects from a visitor to catertrax.com (“you”) will only be used by CaterTrax to service your account and/or provide you with information on CaterTrax products and services. The forms on catertrax.com are used to capture contact information.

What is Personal Data?

Under the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“EU GDPR”): Personal Data is defined as “any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.”  
Special Categories of Personal Data.

Certain data is classified under the EU GDPR as special categories and for purposes of this statement are referred to as “Sensitive Personal Data”:

• Racial  
• Ethnic origin  
• Political Opinions  
• Religious Beliefs  
• Trade-union membership  
• Genetic Data  
• Biometric Data  
• Health Data  
• Data concerning a natural person’s sex life  
• Sexual orientation  
• Other

## Why Does CaterTrax Need to Collect and Store Personal Data?

In order for CaterTrax to provide adequate follow up regarding doing business or potential business with a client/prospect, we capture minimal information so that we can conduct business.

The Personal Data CaterTrax may collect includes:

• Your name  
• Your e-mail address  
• Your phone number(s)  
• Other personal or preference information you provide to CaterTrax

In any event, CaterTrax is committed to ensuring that the information it collects and uses is appropriate for this purpose, and does not constitute an invasion of your privacy. CaterTrax may pass your Personal Data on to its third-party service providers who are contracted to CaterTrax (“Contractors”) in the course of dealing with you. Those Contractors are obliged to keep your details secure, and use them only to fulfil the service they provide you on our behalf. Once your service need has been satisfied or the case has been closed, they will dispose of the details in accordance with CaterTrax’s procedures. If CaterTrax wishes to pass your Sensitive Personal Data onto a third party it will only do so once CaterTrax has obtained your consent, unless legally CaterTrax is required to provide the data.

## How CaterTrax Uses Your Information

CaterTrax will process – that means collect, store and use – the information you provide in a manner that is compatible with the EU GDPR. CaterTrax will endeavor to keep your information accurate and up to date and not keep it for longer than is necessary. In some instances, the law sets the length of time information has to be kept, but in most cases CaterTrax will use its discretion to ensure that it does not keep records outside of our normal business requirements.

Our aim is not to be intrusive, and CaterTrax undertakes not to ask irrelevant or unnecessary questions. Moreover, the information you provide will be subject to rigorous measures and procedures to minimize the risk of unauthorized access or disclosure.

Using your Personal Data:

CaterTrax will use the information you provide for the following purposes:  
• To contact you regarding your inquiry  
• To send you company and product related information

## Consent to Process Your Personal Data

By utilizing the CaterTrax system, you are giving CaterTrax permission to perform those actions and to process your Personal Data as described above. You may withdraw consent at any time by submitting a request to CaterTrax using this [form](https://catertrax.com/eugdpr/). As a result of your request, you will be given a form to complete which will provide CaterTrax with your withdrawal consent to process data per the EU GDPR.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us at 1.800.975.8729 or visit our [Contact Us page](http://catertrax.com/get-to-know-us/contact-us/) to email a question immediately.
